whatusersdo.com 2013-06-21

# Privacy Policy

whatusersdo Ltd recognises that your privacy is very important to you. We will never rent, sell or otherwise disclose any of your personal information to a third party without your consent. 

This document describes our privacy policy and you should read it in conjunction with the Terms and Conditions. 

We collect the following personal information from clients: 

Email address Contact details 

We use this information to: 

  * Communicate with you
  * Enable you to login
  * Let you see invoices and billing information

We collect the following personal information from testers: 

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Screen name
  * Demographic information
  * Postal address
  * Computer information (e.g. Operating System)
  * Only where you have been invited to and have explicitly joined a specific customer panel, to share your email address with the customer only for the administration of Third Party Recompense (e.g. vouchers, charitable donations) arrangements

We use this information to: 

  * Communicate with you
  * Match you to the demographic profiles requested by clients
  * Show clients your year of birth, gender and screen name
  * Show clients system information about your computer e.g. Operating System, Browser version

### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of text stored on a computer by a web browser. We use cookies to make whatusersdo.com easier to use, by making it easy to login for example. 

### IP Address

We record your IP address when you visit our site. 

### Disclosure for Legal Reasons

We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to third parties which seek the disclosure of it, and which make a legally compliant request for its disclosure. 

### Aggregate Statistical Information

We may collect aggregated statistical information in order to improve our service to you. This data does not contain personally identifying information, such as your name or email address. 

### Data Retention

We will retain your data data only as long as is necessary for the purposes to which you consent under the Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy, or as is required by applicable law, and then we will delete it. 

### Credit Card processing

Payments by clients to whatusersdo Ltd are securely processed by Nochex Online Payment Services. You can read their privacy policy here: http://nochex.com/privacy/ 

### External Sites

This website contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content of those sites and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of those sites. 

### Changes

From time to time, whatusersdo Ltd will may edit this policy in accordance with potential changes to our business and as required by law. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. 

### Contact

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please Contact us. 

### Information Commission

There is more information about personal information and your rights at the Information Commissioner's Office website at http://www.ico.gov.uk/ 

### Need Help?

Read the [FAQ](http://www.whatusersdo.com/user-experience-testing/user-experience-testing-frequently-asked-questions.php) or [get in touch](http://www.whatusersdo.com/user-experience-testing/whatusersdo-contact-information-how-to-get-in-touch.php) with a member of our team
